Lewes
My heirloom
The gold ring is gone
Maybe last night
I left it in the mixing room
Open the door
I'll go in and look
Is that so
Then go look for it quickly
Not here
Maybe I remembered wrong
I'll look elsewhere
Oh no
My feed
Old man
What's going on
Dad
Are you okay
I'm getting old
My legs are unsteady
I couldn't hold the basin
Lewes
I'm so useless
I got water on the feed
Look at these
Can they still be used
No
It's all wet
If the forest frogs eat this
They will get sick
You're good for nothing
Only good at messing things up
I brought you here to work
But you're just making a mess
All these forest frogs
What will they eat
We can't let them starve
It's all my fault
Is there anything you can do right
Huh
Mom
Stop it
Dad didn't mean it
I will just
remix the feed
Sorry for the trouble, Lewes
Let's go